William Francis Gray Swann Papers 1903-1962 Mss.B.Sw1
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, 1916-1958; 3.0 Linear feet
  - Kelly, Harry C., 1961; 1 item (Box 26)
  - Kelly, M. J., 1947; 1 item (Box 26)
  - Kelly, Mary Isabel, 1925-1953; 3 folders (Box 26)
    - Folder 1, 1925-1946 (Box 26)
    - Folder 2, 1948-1951 (Box 26)
    - Folder 3, 1952-1953 (Box 26)
  - Kemble, Edwin C., 1925-1941; 19 items (Box 26)
  - Kempton, Winifred, 1956; 1 item (Box 26)
  - Kendall, Burton W., 1926; 1 item (Box 26)
  - Kenna, Howard, 1931-1932; 3 items (Box 26)
  - Kennedy, Fitzroy, 1948; 2 items (Box 26)
  - Kennelly, A. E., 1924-1933; 11 items (Box 26)
  - Kennelly, Martin H., 1951; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Kenschaft, Roland P., 1961; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Kensill, Frank V., 1947; 9 items (Box 27)
  - Kent, C. V., 1934-1947; 4 items (Box 27)
  - Kenyon, John N., 1950; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Kerby, Ernest F., 1937-1939; 4 items (Box 27)
  - Kerbey, McFall, 1936-1937; 12 items (Box 27)
  - Kerlin, E. G., 1945; 3 items (Box 27)
  - Kern, Francis H., 1936; 2 items (Box 27)
  - Kerr, Donald C., 1939; 2 items (Box 27)
  - Kersey, Vierling, 1948; 2 items (Box 27)
  - Kertess, Ferdinand A., 1 item (Box 27)
  - Kester, F. C., 1922; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Ketterer, Gustave, 1938; 2 items (Box 27)
  - Keulegan, G. H., 1954-1955; 2 items (Box 27)
  - Key, Algene, 1946-1947; 2 items (Box 27)
  - Kidd, William H., 1958; 3 items (Box 27)
  - Kidder, Peabody & Company, 1943-1947; 26 items (Box 27)
  - Kieft, E., 1932-1939; 3 items (Box 27)
  - Kildare, H. G., 1939; 2 items (Box 27)
  - Killian, Thomas J., 1931-1961; 3 folders (Box 27)
    - Folder 1, 1931 (Box 27)
    - Folder 2, 1932 (Box 27)
    - Folder 3, 1953-1961 (Box 27)
  - Kimball, Herbert H., 1930; 7 items (Box 27)
  - Kimmell, Mrs., 1924; 1 item (Box 27)
  - King, Esther B. Weston, 1954-1957; 16 items (Box 27)
  - King, Louis V., 1931-1932; 4 items (Box 27)
  - King, R. W., 1937; 2 items (Box 27)
  - King, Robert, 1935; 4 items (Box 27)
  - King, Russell B., 1945-1954; 35 items (Box 27)
  - King, Wilson, 1952; 2 items (Box 27)
  - Kingdon, K. H., 1946; 6 items (Box 27)
  - Kingman, Russell B, 1952; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Kingslake, Hilda G., 1961; 2 items (Box 27)
  - Kinmaer, Willis H., 1957-1959; 15 items (Box 27)
  - Kirk, Raymond E., 1941; 7 items (Box 27)
  - Kirkendall, Ernest, 1946; 2 items (Box 27)
  - Kirkpatrick, P. H., 1945; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Kivarik, Alexis F., 1923; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Klein, Donald R., 1958; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Kleinberg, Ernest, 1941; 4 items (Box 27)
  - Klemin, Alexander, 1938-1945; 10 items (Box 27)
  - Kline, J. R., 1946-1952; 7 items (Box 27)
  - Klint, R. V., 1956; 3 items (Box 27)
  - Kloos, G., 1943; 2 items (Box 27)
  - Klopsteg, Paul, 1922-1952; 6 items (Box 27)
    Rapid x-ray detection (1943)
  - Klyce, S., 1926; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Knapp, David G., 1953; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Knipp, Julian K., 1942; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Kniseley, James E., 1958; 3 items (Box 27)
  - Knowlton, David C., 1948; 2 items (Box 27)
  - Knowlsen, T. Sharper, 1931; 4 items (Box 27)
  - Knox, William J., 1954; 2 items (Box 27)
  - Knudtson, Jerry, 1957; 2 items (Box 27)
  - Knutson, H. C., 1946; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Kobler, Richard, 1940; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Koch, W. R., 1938; 3 items (Box 27)
  - Kohler, William, 1956-1958; 3 items (Box 27)
  - Kolstad, George A., 1951-1958; 29 items (Box 27)
  - Koning, Menno G., 1953; 1 item (Box 27)
  - Koop, Theodore F., 1947; 8 items (Box 27)
    Cosmic ray flights
  - Korchmaros, G., Jr., 1951; 8 items (Box 27)
  - Korff, Serge A., 1933-1958; 8 folders (Box 27)
    - Folder 1, 1933 (Box 27)
    - Folder 2, 1938-1940 (Box 27)
    - Folder 3, 1941 (Box 27)
    - Folder 4, 1942 (Box 27)
    - Folder 5, 1943 Jan.-June (Box 27)
    - Folder 6, 1943 July-Dec. (Box 27)
    - Folder 7, 1944-1946 (Box 27)
    - Folder 8, 1947-1958 (Box 27)
  - Kornblueh, Igho H., 1961; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Kosch, Lewis F., Col., 1943-1944; 12 items (Box 28)
  - Kotliar, Abraham M., 1950; 2 items (Box 28)
  - Kotterman, C. A., 1923; 6 items (Box 28)
  - Koussevitzky, Serge, 1943; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Kovács, Imre, 1948; 2 items (Box 28)
  - Kovanik, Gloria F., 1925; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Koyl, George Simpson, 1941-1942; 2 items (Box 28)
  - Kraemer Elmer O., 1937; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Krasner, Sol, 1957-1959; 6 items (Box 28)
  - Kratz, Paul H., 1948-1955; 49 items (Box 28)
  - Krause, E. H., 1954-1955; 5 items (Box 28)
  - Krentzlin, L. L., 1956; 2 items (Box 28)
  - Kretschmar, George G., 1954; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Krey, A. C., 1939; 2 items (Box 28)
  - Krieger, K. A., 1951; 4 items (Box 28)
  - Kruger, P. Gerald, 1951; 2 items (Box 28)
  - Krumbein, 1944-1950; 2 items (Box 28)
  - Kuper, Mariette, 1947; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Kurtz, S. S., 1942; 2 items (Box 28)
  - Kurtzner, Edward T., 1945-1946; 5 items (Box 28)
  - LaBudde, Kenneth J., 1961; 3 items (Box 28)
  - Ladenburg, R., 1930; 2 items (Box 28)
  - Laffitte, R., 1950; 2 items (Box 28)
  - Lagemann, Robert, 1950; 2 items (Box 28)
  - LaGorce, John O., 1946-1950; 3 items (Box 28)
  - Lal, Gobind Behari, 1935-1955; 29 items (Box 28)
  - Lambert, Walter D., 1960; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Lammers, M. B., 1946; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Lamoureux, Vincent B., 1950; 4 items (Box 28)
  - Landé, Alfred, 1937-1955; 18 items (Box 28)
  - Landis, H., 1945; 2 items (Box 28)
  - Landsberg, H. E., 1947; 4 items (Box 28)
  - Landshoff, Werner, 1955; 5 items (Box 28)
    Includes photo of grave of Diran Alexanian
  - Lange, Harry E., 1953; 2 items (Box 28)
  - Lapp, R. E., 1943-1949; 6 items (Box 28)
  - Lark-Horovitz, K., 1932-1952; 4 folders (Box 28)
    - Folder 1, 1932-1934 (Box 28)
    - Folder 2, 1935-1936 (Box 28)
    - Folder 3, 1937-1945 (Box 28)
    - Folder 4, 1946-1952 (Box 28)
  - Larson, Dorothy Jane, 1939; 4 items (Box 28)
    Life Magazine
  - Larson, W. O., 1922; 2 items (Box 28)
    Includes Carl W. Stomberg's ssay "The relation of surface tension to hemolysis," in submission for the Medal of the St. Paul Institute
  - Laslett, L. Jackson, 1952-1953; 6 items (Box 28)
  - Latham, H. S., 1937-1948; 38 items (Box 28)
  - Laue, Max Von, 1931-1932; 7 items (Box 28)
  - Laughlin, M. P., 1939; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Laurence, William L., 1944-1957; 7 items (Box 28)
  - Lauritsen, Charles C., 1955-1957; 6 items (Box 28)
  - Lawrence, Ernest O., 1933-1957; 41 items (Box 28)
  - Lawton, W. S., 1957; 4 items (Box 28)
  - Leaf, Helen, 1937; 2 items (Box 28)
  - Leahy, W. H., Adm., 1948; 2 items (Box 28)
  - Lear, John, 1960; 4 items (Box 28)
  - Lee, Theron, Jr., 1934; 3 items (Box 28)
  - Leeson, M., 1954-1955; 2 items (Box 28)
  - LeGalley, Donald P., 1933-1934; 11 items (Box 28)
  - Lehigh University, 1932; 14 items (Box 28)
  - Lehnert, Bo, 1956-1958; 12 items (Box 29)
    Includes TMs Preliminary version of the Discussions at the IAU Symposium on Electromagnetic Phenomena in Cosmical Physics
  - Lehr, Herbert M., 1948-1951; 33 items (Box 29)
    Re: B29 flights for cosmic ray studies
  - Leipper, Alex D., 1944-1946; 4 items (Box 29)
  - Leisen, Doris, 1940-1941; 13 items (Box 29)
  - Leland, O. M., 1922; 4 items (Box 29)
    Submissions for the St. Paul Inst. Medal: "Food coloring" and "The benzylation of carbazole"
  - Leland, Waldo G., 1944-1946; 14 items (Box 29)
  - Lemon, Harvey B., 1924; 2 items (Box 29)
  - Lenschner, A. O., 1919; 5 items (Box 29)
  - Lenzen, Victor F., 1935; 2 items (Box 29)
  - Leonard, Clifford S., 1936; 1 item (Box 29)
  - Leonard, Florence, 1934-1935; 4 items (Box 29)
  - LePage, Wynn Laurence, 1950-1961; 15 items (Box 29)
  - Lernor, Joseph, 1939; 1 item (Box 29)
  - Lester, Robert M., 1939; 3 items (Box 29)
  - Levens, G. H., 1923; 1 item (Box 29)
  - Lever, Althea, 1946; 2 items (Box 29)
  - Levick, L. E., 1936; 2 items (Box 29)
  - Levin, Boris, 1960; 5 items (Box 29)
  - Levinson, Carl, 1958; 2 items (Box 29)
  - Levinson, John, 1948; 2 items (Box 29)
  - Levitan, Nelson, 1935; 2 items (Box 29)
  - Levitt, I. M., 1954-1957; 5 items (Box 29)
  - Levy, Bert W., 1951; 2 items (Box 29)
  - Levy, Paul W., 1955; 2 items (Box 29)
  - Lewallen, V., 1950; 3 items (Box 29)
  - Lewis, Bernard, 1947; 1 item (Box 29)
  - Lewis, F. A., 1949; 2 items (Box 29)
  - Lewis, John F. Jr., 1941; 3 items (Box 29)
  - Library of Congress, 1938; 3 items (Box 29)
  - Liddell, Urner -- Folder 1, 1946-1953; 8 folders (Box 29)
    Office of Naval Research
    - Folder 1, 1946 (Box 29)
    - Folder 2, 1947 Jan.-June (Box 29)
    - Folder 3, 1947 July-Oct. (Box 29)
    - Folder 4, 1947 Nov.-Dec. (Box 29)
    - Folder 5, 1948 (Box 29)
    - Folder 6, 1949 (Box 29)
    - Folder 7, 1950 (Box 29)
    - Folder 8, 1951-1953 (Box 29)
  - Liebau, Helene H., 1946; 2 items (Box 29)
    My Faith
  - Life Magazine, 1937; 1 item (Box 29)
  - Lilienthal, David E., 1950; 2 items (Box 29)
  - Lind, David A., 1951; 2 items (Box 29)
  - Lind, S. C., 1936; 3 items (Box 29)
  - Lindsay, John D., 1945-1946; 3 items (Box 29)
  - Lindsay, R. Bruce, 1940-1956; 40 items (Box 29)
  - Linford, Leon B., 1930; 5 items (Box 29)
  - Lingelbach, William Ezra, 1944; 2 items (Box 29)
  - Lingenfelter, R. E., 1952-1953; 4 items (Box 29)
  - Linstead, Patrick, 1956-1960; 7 items (Box 29)
  - Lipman, M. R., 1944-1958; 17 items (Box 29)
  - Lipman, Raoul, 1935-1936; 21 items (Box 29)
  - Liversidge, H. P., 1941; 1 item (Box 30)
  - Livingston, M. Stanley, 1948; 5 items (Box 30)
    Re: Brookhaven magnetron and synchrotron
  - Lloyd, F. M., 1947; 8 items (Box 30)
    Includes photo of Swann in lab and his c.v.
  - Loeb, Leonard B., 1925-1929; 4 items (Box 30)
  - Loewenstein, George, 1951-1952; 15 items (Box 30)
  - Loftus, George H., 1949; 12 items (Box 30)
  - Loh, Zung-Nyi, 1925; 1 item (Box 30)
  - Lohr, Lenox R., 1952-1953; 9 items (Box 30)
  - Lomax, Emma, 1959; 2 items (Box 30)
  - Long, Percy W., 1943; 3 items (Box 30)
  - Longacre, Andrew, 1928-1960; 23 items (Box 30)
  - Longstaffe, Harry D., 1931-1932; 3 items (Box 30)
  - Loofbourow, John R., 1945; 3 items (Box 30)
  - Loomis, Alfred L., 1927-1931; 41 items (Box 30)
  - Loomis, F. W., 1942-1950; 25 items (Box 30)
  - Lord, Mrs. Charles L., 1940; 1 item (Box 30)
  - Lorrain, Paul, 1958; 1 item (Box 30)
  - Loud, Robert, 1960; 1 item (Box 30)
  - Loudis, Anthony J., 1939-1944; 7 items (Box 30)
  - Loughran, Clayton D., 1960; 2 items (Box 30)
  - Louw, G. D., 1946; 2 items (Box 30)
  - Love, William F., 1952; 1 item (Box 30)
  - Lowan, Arnold N., 1945-1946; 6 items (Box 30)
  - Lowensen, C. K., 1932; 16 items (Box 30)
  - Lowery, Martin J., 1935-1936; 2 items (Box 30)
  - Lubkin, Elihu, 1944-1947; 4 items (Box 30)
  - Lucas, F. F., 1940; 2 items (Box 30)
  - Luce, Clare Booth, 1945-1946; 7 items (Box 30)
    Nuclear arms control
  - Ludlum, David M., 1951; 6 items (Box 30)
  - Lukens, Hiram S., 1937-1955; 4 items (Box 30)
    Inelastic scattering of neutrons
  - Lull, Roger E., 1959; 3 items (Box 30)
    Includes TMsS "A case for antigravity" originally sent to George M. Rideout
  - Luquer, Lynch, 1936; 2 items (Box 30)
    Bust of Lord Kelvin given to Smithsonian Institution
  - Lyman, Theodore, 1952; 1 item (Box 30)
  - Lynch, Don W., 1944; 4 items (Box 30)
  - Lynch, Dorothy S., 1936; 2 items (Box 30)
  - Lynn, George, 1925-1926; 2 items (Box 30)
  - Lyon, Richard H., 1952; 1 item (Box 30)
  - Lyttleton, R. A., 1960; 12 items (Box 30)
  - MacAdam, David, 1932; 12 items (Box 30)
  - McCabe, Frederick, 1936; 2 items (Box 30)
  - McCarty, L. E., 1924-1934; 13 items (Box 30)
  - McClarren, Ralph H., 1954-1956; 3 items (Box 30)
  - McClenahan, Howard, 1925-1935; 46 items (Box 30)
  - McConnell, R. A., 1951-1952; 20 items (Box 30)
  - McCormack, John W., 1953-1958; 7 items (Box 30)
  - McCrea, R. H., 1913; 2 items (Box 30)
  - McCue, J. J. G., 1949; 2 items (Box 30)
  - McDermott, Jack C., 1948; 4 items (Box 30)
  - McDonald, Ellice, 1935-1954; 3 folders (Box 31)
    - Folder 1, 1935-1937 (Box 31)
      Cyclotron
    - Folder 2, 1938-1939 (Box 31)
    - Folder 3, 1943-1954 (Box 31)
  - McElrath George, 1935; 5 items (Box 31)
  - McGiffert, James, 1927-1940; 3 folders (Box 31)
    - Folder 1, 1927-1929 (Box 31)
    - Folder 2, 1930-1934 (Box 31)
    - Folder 3, 1936-1940 (Box 31)
  - McGraw-Hill Book Company, 1935; 2 items (Box 31)
  - McKeehan, L. W., 1920-1940; 5 items (Box 31)
  - McKenna, J. V., 1954; 2 items (Box 31)
  - McKenzie, Alexander, 1937-1942; 5 items (Box 31)
  - McKenzie, Lawson M., 1949; 1 item (Box 31)
  - McKibben, J. L., 1955; 5 items (Box 31)
  - Mackin, Robert J., 1954-1956; 26 items (Box 31)
  - McKnew, Thomas W., 1934-1954; 2 folders (Box 31)
    - Folder 1, 1934; 4 items (Box 31)
    - Folder 2, 1935-1954 (Box 31)
  - McLennan, J. C., 1931; 2 items (Box 31)
  - MacMillan Company, 1935-1936 (Box 31)
  - McMillen, J. Howard, 1953-1959; 35 items (Box 31)
  - MacNeille, H. M., 1948-1949; 4 items (Box 31)
  - MacNider, William Deb, 1946; 3 items (Box 31)
  - Mahoney, George F, Jr., 1957; 1 item (Box 31)
  - Maizlish, Israel, 1925-1936; 22 item (Box 31)
  - Malecot, Gaston Louis, 1934; 2 items (Box 31)
  - Malisoff, William Marias, 1932-1933; 5 items (Box 31)
  - Maloney, Agnes, 1932; 1 item (Box 31)
  - Mandeville, C. E., 1950-1954; 12 items (Box 31)
  - Mandeville, C. E. -- Patent application on geiger counter (scintillation) (Box 31)
    Includes correspondence
  - Mandl, Rudi W., 1936; 3 items (Box 31)
    Einstein and relativity
  - Marm, David W., 1927-1928; 6 items (Box 31)
  - Manners, 1911; 1 item (Box 31)
  - Margenau, Henry, 1941-1951; 7 items (Box 32)
  - Marks, Alvin Melville, 1933; 4 items (Box 32)
  - Marsh, Wilbur D., 1956; 4 items (Box 32)
  - Martin, Edward, 1949; 1 item (Box 32)
  - Martin, Frances, 1948; 1 item (Box 32)
  - Martin, Frank G., 1953; 8 items (Box 32)
  - Martin, John R., 1931; 3 items (Box 32)
  - Marvin, Philip, 1957; 1 item (Box 32)
  - Mason, J. R., 1953; 1 item (Box 32)
  - Mason, Max, 1929; 2 items (Box 32)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1931; 13 items (Box 32)
  - Masters, C. W., 1934; 3 items (Box 32)
  - Matsch, L. W., 1952-1953; 9 items (Box 32)
  - Matthiessen, H. F., 1951; 2 items (Box 32)
  - Mauchly, John W., 1933; 4 items (Box 32)
  - Mauchly, Sebastian Jacob, 1929-1930; 13 items (Box 32)
  - Maxwell, L. R., 1931-1932; 16 items (Box 32)
  - May, Louise S., 1930; 1 item (Box 32)
  - Mayer, Philip F., 1955; 8 items (Box 32)
    Natural religion
  - Maynard, A, T., 1936; 3 items (Box 32)
  - Medoff, Irving, 1955; 3 items (Box 32)
  - Medway, Charles, 1936; 2 items (Box 32)
  - Meek, John M., 1939; 6 items (Box 32)
  - Meeker, George H., 1935-1936; 13 items (Box 32)
  - Mees, C. E. Kenneth, 1943-1951; 9 items (Box 32)
  - Meeser, R. H., 1954-1955; 2 items (Box 32)
  - Meijer, Robert R., 1950; 4 items (Box 32)
  - Mendenhall, C. E. and Max Mason, 1922; 1 item (Box 32)
  - Merriam, John C., 1932-1934; 2 items (Box 32)
  - Merritt, E., 1916; 3 items (Box 32)
  - Merrymon, William W., 1924-1951; 11 items (Box 32)
  - Metzger, F. R., 1956; 2 items (Box 32)
  - Michels, Walter C., 1959-1961; 9 items (Box 32)
  - Michelson, A. A., 1921-1924; 12 items (Box 32)
  - Mickelson, Robert L., 1945; 3 items (Box 32)
  - Mickle, J. R., 1931-1937; 5 items (Box 32)
  - Mierow, C. C., 1926; 1 item (Box 32)
  - Military Engineer, 1933-1934; 7 items (Box 32)
  - Miller, B. L., 1951; 2 items (Box 32)
  - Miller, C. William, 1952; 2 items (Box 32)
  - Miller, D. B., 1946; 1 item (Box 32)
  - Miller, Dayton C., 1921-1937; 5 items (Box 32)
  - Miller, Hugh H., 1958; 1 item (Box 32)
  - Miller, Maynard M., 1946-1949; 17 items (Box 32)
  - Millikan, Robert A., 1914-1952; 29 items (Box 32)
  - Millman, S., 1948; 2 items (Box 32)
  - Milner, C. J., 1953; 3 items (Box 32)
  - Milner, F. R., 1953; 1 item (Box 32)
  - Milner, S. R., 1923-1936; 7 items (Box 32)
  - Mimno, H. R., 1945; 3 items (Box 32)
  - Minar, C. K. D., 1955; 2 items (Box 32)
  - Miquelle, Renee Longy, 1940; 2 items (Box 32)
  - Miskjian, V. G., 1932-1934; 16 items (Box 32)
  - Mitchell, Allen C. G., 1930-1938; 24 items (Box 32)
  - Mitchell, Don, 1955; 2 items (Box 32)
  - Mitchell, George, 1954; 8 items (Box 32)
  - Mitchell, John J., 1954; 2 items (Box 32)
  - Mitchell, Madeline, 1936; 2 items (Box 32)
  - Mitchell, S. A., 1936; 1 item (Box 32)
  - Mittelstaedt, George S., 1948; 2 items (Box 32)
  - Moe, Henry Allen, 1946; 3 items (Box 32)
  - Moennig, William If, Jr., 1944-1959; 4 items (Box 32)
  - Mohler, F. L., 1934; 2 items (Box 32)
  - Moller, R. A., 1953; 3 items (Box 32)
  - Moloney, Thomas J., 1934; 2 items (Box 32)
  - Monsma, J. C., 1957; 2 items (Box 32)
  - Montgomery, Carol G., 1932-1946; 2 folders (Box 33)
    - Folder 1, 1932-1934 (Box 33)
    - Folder 2, 1935-1946 (Box 33)
  - Montgomery, Franz, 1932; 2 items (Box 33)
  - Moon, Philip B., 1956-1957; 10 items (Box 33)
  - Moore, Elizabeth F., 1960; 4 items (Box 33)
  - Moore, Herbert, 1960; 1 item (Box 33)
  - Moore, Ida S., 1941; 1 item (Box 33)
  - Moore, John, 1957; 1 item (Box 33)
  - Moore, Philip S., 1946; 2 items (Box 33)
  - Moreno, E. Pina, 1948; 3 items (Box 33)
  - Morey, Frank R., 1945-1946; 8 items (Box 33)
  - Morgan, F. Haydn, 1952-1953; 5 items (Box 33)
  - Morgan, Marshall S., 1924-1934; 4 items (Box 33)
  - Morgan, Vernon William, Jr., 1954-1955; 2 items (Box 33)
  - Moritz, Ernst, 1956; 11 items (Box 33)
  - Morris, Berenice T., 1949; 5 items (Box 33)
  - Morris, Don, 1945; 10 items (Box 33)
  - Morris, Frederick, III, 1955; 2 items (Box 33)
  - Morris, J. C., 1941-1942; 15 items (Box 33)
  - Morris, Peter A., 1946-1949; 17 items (Box 33)
  - Morris, Samuel R., 1933; 2 items (Box 33)
  - Morris, W., 1932; 2 items (Box 33)
  - Morrison, G. H., 1934; 4 items (Box 33)
  - Morrison, O. C., 1943; 3 items (Box 33)
  - Morrison, Orville C., 1951; 5 items (Box 33)
  - Morse, Jared K., 1924; 1 item (Box 33)
  - Morse, Philip M., 1947; 13 items (Box 33)
  - Moshier, A. T., 1936; 2 items (Box 33)
  - Moss, H., 1924; 1 item (Box 33)
  - Moteff, John, 1951; 2 items (Box 33)
  - Moulds, John F., 1922; 1 item (Box 33)
  - Moulton, F. R., 1928-1950; 2 folders (Box 33)
    - Folder 1, 1928-1935 (Box 33)
    - Folder 2, 1945-1950 (Box 33)
  - Mudd, Stuart, 1958-1962; 8 items (Box 33)
  - Muelder, Milton E., 1951-1952; 3 items (Box 33)
  - Mueller, A. C., 1956; 1 item (Box 33)
  - Müller, Gladys, 1938-1940; 4 items (Box 33)
  - Mulford, Leslie F., 1944; 4 items (Box 33)
  - Mulliken, Robert S., 1946; 1 item (Box 33)
  - Mundell, S. A., 1946; 4 items (Box 33)
  - Murdock, George J., 1936; 2 items (Box 33)
  - Murnaghan, Frances D., 1927; 2 items (Box 33)
  - Murray, D. B., 1936; 1 item (Box 33)
  - Musical Instruments --Correspondence, 1935-1957 (Box 33)
  - Myers, Francis J., 1945-1949; 4 items (Box 33)
  - Myers, I. O., 1958; 4 items (Box 33)
  - Myers, Richmond E., 1955; 2 items (Box 33)
  - Nagashima, Kazuo, 1952; 3 items (Box 33)
  - Nagel, Robert H., 1960; 7 items (Box 33)
  - Nalle, Richard T., 1950; 1 item (Box 33)
  - Narbeth, J. David, 1949-1951; 10 items (Box 33)
  - Nardozza, Edmond H., 1943; 3 items (Box 33)
  - Nason, John W., 1937-1951; 20 items (Box 33)
  - Nathanson, Jerome, 1945; 2 items (Box 33)
    Transcript of interview with Swann on religion and science
  - National Academy of Sciences (U.S.), 1933; 14 items (Box 33)
  - National Broadcasting Company, 1934; 3 items (Box 33)
  - National Geographic Society, 1934; 10 items (Box 33)
  - National Research Council, 1921-1958; 2 folders (Box 33)
    - Folder 1, 1921-1922 (Box 33)
    - Folder 2, 1923-1958 (Box 33)
  - National Science Foundation (U.S.), 1958-1959; 5 items (Box 33)
  - Natural History Magazine, 1935; 1 item (Box 33)
  - Nauheimer, G. Francis, 1934; 4 items (Box 33)
  - Navy Industrial Association, 1947; 1 item (Box 33)
  - Naylor, William S., 1952-1953; 11 items (Box 33)
  - Neathery, Robert W., 1960-1961; 8 items (Box 33)
  - Neave, F. N., 1936; 2 items (Box 33)
  - Necho, Louis, 1951-1952; 8 items (Box 33)
    Re: Marion Stanley Kapelski, inmate at Eastern State Penn.
  - Nellius, Dick, 1958; 3 items (Box 34)
  - Nelson, Ed., 1961; 16 items (Box 34)
  - Nelson, H. F., 1957; 2 items (Box 34)
  - Nester, A. G., 1930; 1 item (Box 34)
  - Netherly, G. P., 1936; 10 items (Box 34)
  - Neuber, Herbert K., 1950; 4 items (Box 34)
  - Neutron Counters, 1942; 2 items (Box 34)
  - Newcomet, William S., 1943-1948; 5 items (Box 34)
  - Newgarden, Albert, 1957; 3 items (Box 34)
  - Newman, J. A., 1958; 1 item (Box 34)
  - Newman, Jay, 1956; 3 items (Box 34)
  - New York Museum of Science and Industry, 1933; 3 items (Box 34)
    Geiger counter
  - Nichols, Dudley, 1929-1958; 26 items (Box 34)
    Includes photo of Nichols
  - Nichols, Roy Franklin, 1958; 2 items (Box 34)
  - Nicholson, S. B., 1946; 2 items (Box 34)
  - Nielsen, Walter M., 1925-1951; 2 folders (Box 34)
    - Folder 1, 1925-1933 (Box 34)
    - Folder 2, 1934-1951 (Box 34)
  - Niemann, Minna, 1933; 4 items (Box 34)
  - Noonan, Julia, 1953; 4 items (Box 34)
  - Norcross, Cleveland, 1943-1949; 9 items (Box 34)
  - Nordheim, L. W., 1953-; 13tems (Box 34)
  - Norinder, Harold, 1920-1956; 10 items (Box 34)
  - Northover, Ruth, 1933; 3 items (Box 34)
  - Norwalk Company, 1927; 1 item (Box 34)
  - O'Brien, Brian, 1937-1938; 6 items (Box 34)
  - O'Brien, J. B., 1924; 1 item (Box 34)
  - O'Connor, Cornelius, 1946; 3 items (Box 34)
  - O'Connor, R. T., 1959-1960; 9 items (Box 34)
  - O'Conor, John S., 1951-1957; 8 items (Box 34)
  - O'Dea, Catherine, 1952; 3 items (Box 34)
  - Odishaw, Hugh, 1959-1962; 5 items (Box 34)
  - O'Donnell, Eugene J., 1955; 4 items (Box 34)
  - Oehser, Paul H., 1952-1961; 26 items (Box 34)
  - Offenbacher, Elmer L., 1957-1961; 18 items (Box 34)
  - Ogden, Benjamin V., 1944; 7 items (Box 34)
  - Ogburn, William F., 1925; 1 item (Box 34)
  - Ohio State University, 1930-1934 (Box 34)
  - O'Keefe, J., 1959; 1 item (Box 34)
  - Okeson, Walter R., 1935; 1 item (Box 34)
  - Oliphant, M. L., 1948; 4 items (Box 34)
  - Olmsted, Allen S., 2nd, 1954-1955; 9 items (Box 34)
  - Olsen, Harry E., 1942; 1 item (Box 34)
  - Oncley, Paul, n.d.; 1 item (Box 34)
  - Onderdonk, Francis S., 1951; 2 items (Box 34)
  - O'Neill, J. J., 1952-1953; 4 items (Box 34)
    Includes cy of O'Neill's "Gravitational and electrical fields dynamically equated"
  - Oort, J. H., 1957; 1 item (Box 34)
  - Oppenheimer, J. Robert, 1947; 1 item (Box 34)
  - Oppenheimer, Jane M., 1955; 7 items (Box 34)
  - Optical Society of America, 1928-1932; 3 items (Box 34)
  - O'Rahilly, A., 1932-1938; 6 items (Box 34)
  - Ordway, Frederick I., III, 1955; 2 items (Box 34)
  - Ormer, B. W. Van, 1943; 2 items (Box 34)
  - Orowan, Egon, 1950-1955; 7 items (Box 34)
  - Ortmann, Otto, 1943; 3 items (Box 34)
  - Osbahr Bernard F., 1952-1953; 3 items (Box 34)
  - Oser, Joseph I., 1951; 2 items (Box 34)
  - Osgood, Thomas H., 1938-1954; 20 items (Box 34)
  - Osol, Arthur, 1951; 11 items (Box 34)
  - Osterman, Marvin B., 1950; 2 items (Box 34)
  - Otting, William J., 1954-1957; 4 items (Box 34)
  - Overhage, Carl F. J., 1950-1951; 9 items (Box 34)
  - Overbeck, C. J., 1941; 3 items (Box 34)
  - Overman, Ralph T., 1951; 1 item (Box 34)
  - Owen, Louis E., 1957-1960; 5 items (Box 34)
  - Page, Leigh, 1923-1948; 28 items (Box 35)
  - Paine, Charles, 1931; 4 items (Box 35)
  - Paisley, T. E., 1961; 1 item (Box 35)
  - Palmer, Archie M., 1933; 5 items (Box 35)
  - Palmer, Ronald, 1931; 2 items (Box 35)
  - Palmer, Samuel, 1940; 1 item (Box 35)
  - Panama. Consulate, 1946; 11 items (Box 35)
  - Panay, T. N., 1937; 3 items (Box 35)
  - Parker, S. H., 1954-1955; 4 items (Box 35)
  - Parks, W. George, 1950; 6 items (Box 35)
  - Parrish, W., 1942; 6 items (Box 35)
  - Parsegian, V. L., 1954; 1 item (Box 35)
  - Partlo, F. L., 1949; 3 items (Box 35)
  - Patai, Imre F., 1948-1949; 13 items (Box 35)
  - Patterson, Bob, 1955; 1 item (Box 35)
  - Patterson, John C., 1947; 2 items (Box 35)
  - Patterson, R. A., 1946; 2 items (Box 35)